A Guide to the Richmond (Va.) Office of the City Engineer, Records, 1809-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Architectural drawings and plans, 1809-1975.
  - Sewer / Drainage - [Drainage study of area between Monroe Park and the Penitentiary], 3-C-2, n.d., Dimensions: 37-1/2 x 52 in. - 95 x 132 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 62)
  - Sewer / Drainage - [Plan of elevations and roads in East End], 20-A_2, n.d., Dimensions: 11-1/2 x 18-1/2 in. - 29 x 47 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 60)
  - Sewer / Drainage - Sketch Showing the Position of the Sewer, Water, and Gas Pipes / in 7th Street Crossing Broad Street, 3-A-2, n.d., Dimensions: 9-1/4 x 39-1/4 in. - 23 x 99 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink an red ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 60)
  - Sewer / Drainage - This plan represents location of sewer commencing near corner / of Cary and 11th. Streets, and running to the tail race of Gallego / Mills, in Canal Street, 60-B-5, n.d., Dimensions: 19-1/4 x 34-1/2 in. - 49 x 88 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 59)
  - Sewer / Drainage - Standard Cross Section for Bacon's Quarter Branch / from Spottswood Avenue to Hermitage Rd., 55-A-1, n.d., Dimensions: 11-1/2 x 11-1/2 in. - 29 x 29 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 59)
  - Sewer / Drainage - [Drainage study for Shockoe Bottom], 14-D-4, n.d., Dimensions: 19-1/4 x 23-1/2 in. - 49 x 60 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 62)
  - Sewer / Drainage - [Sections of three large sewer lines], 51-C-1, n.d., Dimensions: 21-3/4 x 33-1/2 in. - 55 x 85 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 63)
  - Street - Diagram of grades for Byrd Street, 9-A-6, 1857, Dimensions: 10-1/2 x 16-1/4 in. - 27 x 41 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Ink on paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 97)
    Drawn By: M. Bates. Supt Streets
  - Street - [Survey of Adams Street from Grace / to Franklin], 12-A-6, 1871, Dimensions: 12-1/2 x 15-1/4 in. - 32 x 39 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: Ink and red ink on ruled paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
    Drawn By: Chas. H. Dimmock / City Surveyor
  - Street - [Plan of a part of the block bounded by Cary, 9th, and Canal streets], 4-A-5, 1886, Dimensions: 15-3/4 x 33 in. - 40 x 84 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil and India ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 69)
    Drawn By: S. Edward Bates / Jackson Bolton
  - Street - Proposed Street Along So. Side of Tredegar Works, 10-A-5, 1888, Dimensions: 7-1/4 x 36 in. - 18 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Blueprint with red ink notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 69)
  - Street - Map / of / Tredegar St. / from / 7th St. to Old Pump House, 10-A-5, 1890, Dimensions: 13-1/2 x 49 in. - 35 x 123 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 69)
  - Street - Plan and Profile / of / Broad Street from 11th to 24th Street, 22-A-2, 1890, Dimensions: 15-3/4 x 47-1/4 in. - 40 x 120 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - [Plat of streets and property owners between Harrison, Park, Franklin, and Lombardy Streets], 44-B-5, 1892, Dimensions: 20 x 34 in. - 51 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 65)
    Drawn By: F.T.B.
  - Street - A Map / of / A Proposed Extension of / Spring Street / showing also the relative position / of same to the Roadway through Va. State / Penitentiary Property., 15-B-5, 1893, Dimensions: 34 x 24-3/4 in. - 86 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: 1 Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen, I blueprint; Sheets: 2 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: P.P. Taliaferro / Asst. City Eng.
  - Street - [Plan of area between Mosby, Pleasants, Marshall, and Broad streets], 29-B-2, 1894, Dimensions: 32 x 37-1/2 in. - 81 x 95; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink on linen with red ink; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
    Drawn By: P.P. Taliaferro / Asst. Eng.
  - Street - A Map showing the general position of Streets / between Broad St. and Bacon Quarter Branch and / Lombardy and Hermitage Road, 23-B-4, 1896, Dimensions: 25 x 39-1/2 in. - 64 x 100 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil, India ink, red ink, and blue ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - A Sketch showing the relative position of / Broad Meadow and Duncan Sts, to the Hermitage Road, 20-C-1, 1896, Dimensions: 20-1/2 x 35-1/4 in. - 52 x 89 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
    Drawn By: P. P. Taliaferro / Asst. Eng.
  - Street - Map / of / Concord Street, 24-A-2, 1896, Dimensions: 11 x 60-1/2 in - 28 x 154 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - Plan of proposed Street 40 ft wide as shown / by dotted lines, extending from Lewis Street opposite / Fulton St. to the Southern Railroad Company's property where it will connect with Chimbarazo Park, 36-A-2, 1899, Dimensions: 25-1/2 x 13 in. - 65 x 33 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
    Drawn By: S. Ed. Bates / Asst. City Engineer
  - Street - [Plan showing lot owners in block bounded by R, Q, 30th and 29th streets], 10-C-2, 1900, Dimensions: 20 x 15 in. - 51 x 38 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink and blue ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Map Showing Encroachments on East Side of 4th Street / between Byrd & Arch Sts., 17-A-1, 1901, Dimensions: 8-1/2 x 25-3/4 in. - 21 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: 1India ink and red ink on linen, 1 India ink and red ink on paper; Sheets: 2 (Folder 69)
  - Street - [Randolph St. between M and N Streets], 39-A-2, 1901, Dimensions: 16-1/2 x 26-1/4 in. - 42 x 67 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 3 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Street Numbers West of First / and Between Broad and Main Sts. / Approved by Committee on Streets / march 17th 1902, 20-B-2, 1902, Dimensions: 20 x 38 in. - 51 x 97 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
  - Street - Brook Avenue / from / Broad St. to Bacon's Quarter Branch, 2-A-2, 1902, Dimensions: 13 x 67-1/2 in. - 33 x 171 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 69)
  - Street - Sketch Showing Change in / Location of Road to Fulton / at Foot of Chimborazo Hill, 14-A-5, 1903, Dimensions: 14 x 8-1/2 in. - 36 x 21 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
  - Street - Revised plan for section between / Park Avenue & Broad, Harrison & Lombardy streets - change noted in red figures, 20-B-2, 1904, Dimensions: 24 x 12-1/4 in. - 61 x 31 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
    Drawn By: Adopted by Committee on Streets / [date] / J. Taylor Stratton / Clerk - Committee
  - Street - A Proposed Pan Widening Franklin St. / to 130 ft. Between Allison St. and the Boulevard, 25-C-2, 1905, Dimensions: 25 x 70-1/2 in. - 64 x 179 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 4 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Map showing the location of the Crematory lot and / the streets in the vicinity with the present road / shaded in green, 47-B-4, 1906, Dimensions: 29-1/4 x 20-1/2 in. - 74 x 51 cm.; Scale: 1" =100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - Map / Showing Oakwood Avenue and the Adjoining / Territory as Made up from the Several Plans of / that Section, 29-C-2, 1906, Dimensions: 25 x 35-1/2 in. - 63 x 90 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Plan and Profile of Curbs around / Richmond Post Office., 50-A-2, 1906, Dimensions: 12 x 17 in. - 30 x 43 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
  - Street - A Portion of the Proposed Plan, Marked 'D', Widening Franklin St. to 130 Ft. Between Allison and Addison Sts, 25-C-2, 1906, Dimensions: 13-1/4 x 18-1/2 in. - 34 x 47 cm.; Scale: 1" = 60'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
    Drawn By: City Eng's Office
  - Street - Map Showing Cedar Street Widened from 48.5 Ft. to 80 Ft. from Park Ave. to Broad St., 28-C-2, 1906, Dimensions: 16-1/2 x 33-3/4 in. - 42 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Plan Showing a Proposed Road / 50' Wide, Extending from the Hermitage / Road to Broad Street Road, 30-D-3, 1906, Dimensions: 24 38 in. - 61 x 96 cm.; Scale: 1" = 200'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: T. Crawford Redd & Bro. / Surveyors and Engineers.
  - Street - [Plan of block between Garrison, Cowardin, 30th and Oakwood streets], 51-B-1, 1906, Dimensions: 19 x 37-1/2 in. - 48 x 95 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
    Drawn By: P.T.T. / Asst.
  - Street - A Map Showing the Land / Necessary to Continue / Oakwood Ave. Straight to / P St., 29-C-2, 1906, Dimensions: 17-1/2 x 20 in. - 44 x 51 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
    Drawn By: P. P. T. / Asst. Eng.
  - Street - Sketch Showing a Close Approximate / of the Location of the Two Dwellings / Now Partly on the Proposed Extension / of Canepa St. to Oakwood Avenue, 29-C-2, 1906, Dimensions: 15-1/2 x 18-1/2 in. - 39 x 47 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Plan and Profiles of Alleys in Block Bounded by Harrison and Morris Sts., 17-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 17-/2 in. - 57 x 44 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink with pencil notations on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan & Profiles of Alley in Block Bounded by / Laurel & Cherry: Spring & China Streets, 23-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 24-1/4 x 33-1/4 in. - 61 x 84 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Map / of / 34th Street / Broad St. to Oakwood Avenue / Showing Adjacent Property Owners on East / and West Sides, 42-C-2, 1907, Dimensions: 17-1/4 x 57 in. - 44 x 145 cm.; Scale: 1" = 60'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Plan / of / Proposed Widening of Cedar St. 43.5 Ft. on West / from / Park Ave. to Grace St, 28-C-2, 1907, Dimensions: 23-3/4 x 54 in. - 60 x 137 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Profiles of Alley from Cedar to Robinson Sts. Between Monument Ave. and Grace St., 24-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 14-3/4 x 19 in. - 37 x 48 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - [Profiles of two alleys between Monument Ave. and Grace streets], 21-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 17-1/2 x 19-3/4 in. - 44 x 50 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Profile of Alley from Walnut to Park St. Between Park and Hanover Aves., 19-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 16-1/4 x 20 in. - 41x 51 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan and Profile of Alleys in Block Bounded by Broad and / Marshall 23rd & 24th Sts., 20-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 22 x 19-1/4 in. - 56 x 49 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Profile of Alley from Meadow to Allison St. / Between / Franklin or Mont. Ave. and Park Ave., 15-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 11 x 26 in. - 28 x 66 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, VA.
  - Street - Map / of the / Proposed Extension / of / Chamberlayne Parkway / from / Calhoun and Cabell Sts / to Adams and Leigh Sts, 49-A-6, 1907, Dimensions: 40-1/2 x 70-1/4 in. - 103 x 178 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink with pencil notations on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / From Original Surveys by / Fontaine Jones / Asst. Engineer
  - Street - A Proposed Plan / Showing Opening of Lombardy St. 60 ft. Wide / From Broad St. to Railroad St., 27-C-3, 1907, Dimensions: 29-1/2 x 37 in. - 75 x 94 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Plan and Profile of Alleys in Block Bounded by Clay and Leigh Sts. / First and St. James St., 14-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 22 x 30 in. - 56 x 76 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink and red ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan and Profile of Alley Extending From Allison to Addison St. Between Monument Ave. and Park Ave., 18-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 22 x 34-3/4 in. - 56 x 88 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Profile of Alley between 5th & 6th, Orleans & Louisiana Streets, 6-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 9-1/4 x 13-1/2 in. - 24 x 34 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond, Va. / C.L. Todd, Jr. / Ass't Engr
  - Street - Plan and Profiles of Alleys from 30th. To 31st. St. Between Broad and Marshall St., 44-A-1, 1907, Dimensions: 16-1/4 x 23-3/4 in. - 41 x 60 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones, Del.
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Plan & Profile of Broad Street / 12 to 22nd St. / Showing Grade for Proposed Viaduct, 12-A-4, 1907, Dimensions: Various; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 5 (Folder 67)
    Drawn By: City Engr's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones / Asst. City Engr.
  - Street - Plan / of / Extension of Leigh St. / from / 22nd and Scott Sts. To Pickett or 21st St., 45-B-4, 1907, Dimensions: 30 x 32-3/4 in. - 76 x 83 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - Plan of Proposed Alley Extending / from 5th to 6th St. Between Louisiana / and Orleans St., 43-B-4, 1907, Dimensions: 23-1/2 x 34-1/2 in. - 59 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / Plan & Profile of Lombardy St. / Showing Grade for Proposed Viaduct, 46-B-4, 1907, Dimensions: 23 x 33 in. - 58 x 84 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Plan and Profiles of Alleys in Block Bounded by 28th and 29th Sts. And Grace and Broad Sts., 8-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 16-1/2 in. - 57 x 42 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink, red ink, and blue ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan and Profile of Alleys Bounded by Cedar and Robinson St. and Hanover and Ivy Aves., 7-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 23 x 23 in. - 58 x 58 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: 1 India ink, red ink, and blue ink on linen, 1 pencil, red ink, and blue ink on graph paper; Sheets: 2 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Profile of Alley Extending from Cedar St. to Robinson St. Between Kensington St. and Ivy Ave., 13-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 6-1/2 x 17in. - 17 x 43 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Profile of Alley leading Eastwardly from 4th St. Between Grace and Franklin Sts., 5-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 7-3/4 x 13 in. - 20 x 33 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Profile of Alley from 4th to 3rd St. Between Broad and Marshal Sts., 9-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 14 x 16 in. - 35 x 41 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan / of / Proposed Extensions / of / Alison, Lombardy, Clay and Marshall Sts., 39-C-2, 1907, Dimensions: 17-3/4 x 31-1/2 in. - 45 x 80 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Map / of / that part of he Newly Annexed Territory / of the City of Richmond / from the Boulevard / to the Roseneath Road, 34-C-2, 1907, Dimensions: 25 x 37-3/4 in. - 63 x 96 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 3 (Folder 74)
  - Street - [Profiles of intersection of Randolph and 23rd. Street], 24-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 16 x 19 in. - 41 x 48 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan and Profile of Alleys in Block Bounded by Clay and Leigh Sts. / First and St. James Sts., 14-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 24-1/4 x 32 in. - 62 x 81 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan and Profiles of Alleys in Block Bounded by 28th and 29th Sts. And Grace and Broad Sts., 8-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 17 x 17 in. - 43 x 43 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink, red ink, and blue ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan and Profiles of Alleys in Block Bounded by / Floyd and Grove Avenues and Harvie and Plum Sts., 16-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 19-1/2 x 23 in. - 49 x 59 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Plan and Profiles of Alleys from Linden to Harrison St. Between Main and Cary, 11-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 22 x 31 in. - 56 x 79 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink, red ink, blue ink, and pencil notations on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones / Asst. City Engr.
  - Street - Grade Chart / of / Sts. Between Broad and Franklin Sts. / 29th Street and Chimborazo Park, 25-C-3, 1907, Dimensions: 17 x 18 in. - 43 x 46 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 73)
  - Street - Profile of Alley Extending Westerwardly from Fourth St. / Between Franklin & Grace Sts., 10-D-3, 1907, Dimensions: 14 x 13 in. - 35 x 33 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and red ink on graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Map Showing Ground and Grade Elevations / in that Part of The Newly Annexed / Territory Known as 'Duncan Lodge', 35-C-2, 1907, Dimensions: 18 x 24 in. - 46 x 61 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Blueline print; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Map of Tracks / on / Property of West & Robinson / Bounded by / 17th & 18th, Broad & Clay Streets / Richmond, Va., 48-B-4, 1908, Dimensions: 20 x 33-1'/2 in. - 51 x 5 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: Blueprint with red ink notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
    Drawn By: Made in Office of Division Engineer / Eng. Maintenance of Way / C. & O. Ry.
  - Street - A grade chart showing the / elevations and grades of the street Curbs / on 'S' Street or Fairmont Ave, 31-C-3, 1908, Dimensions: 21-1/2 x 37-1/2 in. - 55 x 95 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
    Drawn By: P.P.T. / Ass't City Eng.
  - Street - 33rd. Street. / Showing Encroachments on Proposed East Line, 58-A-2, 1908, Dimensions: 13 x 42-1/2 in. - 33 x 108 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
  - Street - Plot of South West Corner of Harrison / and Main St. and a part of the West Side of Harrison St., 48-B-1, 1908, Dimensions: 21 x 13-3/4 in. - 53 x 3 cm.; Scale: 1"= 10'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 3 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond Va
  - Street - Plan for the Extension of 8th St. to Denny St., 33-B-3, 1908, Dimensions: 32-3/4 x 19-3/4 in. - 83 x 50 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - Plan of Marshall St. Between Hancock & Graham Sts. / Showing Encroachments on the North Side, 32-B-3, 1908, Dimensions: 20 x 35-1/2 in. - 51 x 90 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - [Plan of Williamsburg Ave. between State Street and Louisiana Street], 34-B-3, 1908, Dimensions: 19-1/4 x 34 in. - 49 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - Map of Proposed Road / Connecting / National Cemetery Road with Leigh St. at 35th St., 47-C-3, 1908, Dimensions: 32 x 26-3/4 in. - 81 x 68 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Plan of Cedar St. / from / Monument Ave. to Grace St, 28-C-2, 1908, Dimensions: 8-1/4 x 19 in. - 21 x 48 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Center Grade and Profile of West St. from Cary St. to Park Ave, [No file number], 1908, Dimensions: 10 x 55 in. - 25 x 140 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - D. A Proposed Plan for Shifting the / Alley Between Franklin Street and / Park Avenue, and from Allison to / Cedar Street, 51-A-2, 1908, Dimensions: 10-1/4 x 17 in. - 25 x 43 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
    Drawn By: City Engs. Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones / Del.
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / Plan of the Southeast Corner of Franklin / and Lombardy Street, 34-B-2, 1908, Dimensions: 24-1/4 x 32-1/2 in. - 61 x 82 cm.; Scale: [1" = 20']; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Plan / of / Proposed Steps from 30th St. to / Franklin St. at their Intersection, 43-C-2, 1908, Dimensions: 37-1/2 x 36-3/4 in. - 95 x 93 cm.; Scale: 1/2" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Plan / of / Intersection of 23rd., O, Burton & / Tulip Streets / Showing proposed prolongation of the West / Line of 23rd. St, 55-A-2, 1908, Dimensions: 16-3/4 x 17-1/4 in. - 43 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1" 200'; Media: Pencil, India ink, red ink, and brown ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
    Drawn By: City Engr's Office / Richmond Va.
  - Street - A Map Showing the Land / Necessary to Continue / Oakwood Ave. Straight to / P St., 29-C-3, 1908, Dimensions: 18 x 21-1/2 in. - 46 x 54 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / Map of 18th. St. from Grace to Marshall St. / Showing Encroachments, 59-A-2, 1908, Dimensions: 15-1/2 x 32-1/2 in. - 39 x 82 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
    Drawn By: City Engineers Office / Fontaine Jones / Asst. Engineer
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Map of Cary St. / from / 8th. St. to 9th. St., 46-B-2, 1909, Dimensions: 19 x 31-1/4 in. - 48 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
  - Street - Plan Showing Mrs. S.C. / Acree's Property With Reference / to Venable, Tulip, & 23rd Sts, 37-A-2, 1909, Dimensions: 17-1/2 x 11-1/2 in. - 44 x 30 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Map / of / The South Side of Broad Street / from / Foushee to Jefferson / Showing encroachments of buildings / and the original line, 62-A-2, 1909, Dimensions: 11 x 37-1/4 in. - 28 x 95 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / map of Currie St. and Adjacent Sts. and Property, 53-B-2, 1909, Dimensions: 20 x 22 in. - 51 x 56 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Map of Jefferson St. / From Broad to Marshall St., 45-B-2, 1909, Dimensions: 16 x 38-3/4 in. - 40 x 98 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Fontaine Jones Asst. Engr.
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / Map of South Ninth Street / from / Byrd St. to James River / Showing Approaches, Abutments, Piers, etc, 61-A-2b, 1909, Dimensions: 14 x 56 in. - 36 x 142 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)